<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<component type="desktop-application">
  <id>io.github.sharkwouter.oceanpop</id>
  <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
  <project_license>MIT</project_license>
  <name>OceanPop</name>
  <summary>A relaxing match 3 puzzle game with a twist</summary>

  <description>
    <p>
        Dive into the relaxing world of OceanPop and experience waves of match-3 gameplay with the three modes available! 
    </p>
    <p>   
        Do not get crushed by the tides before completing the 35 levels in regular mode, feel the rush of the currents in challenge mode or just go with the flow of the ocean breeze in relaxed mode!
    </p>
  </description>

  <launchable type="desktop-id">io.github.sharkwouter.oceanpop.desktop</launchable>

  <screenshots>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <caption>OceanPop</caption>
      <image>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/sharkwouter/oceanpop/1.0/screenshot.jpg</image>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>

  <url type="homepage">https://sharkwouter.github.io/oceanpop/</url>
  <developer_name>Wouter "sharkwouter" Wijsman</developer_name>

  <provides>
    <binary>oceanpop</binary>
  </provides>

  <releases>
    <release version="2.0" date="2024-12-19">
      <description>
        <p>Challenge mode levels are now random, making each playthrough different</p>
        <p>Matches required in challenge mode now only increases every 5 levels</p>
        <p>Matches required in challenge mode now maxes out at 25</p>
        <p>Fix the high score screen not showing correctly if standard mode had been completed</p>
        <p>Show how the game works on first run</p>
        <p>Add support for the Wii thanks to mardy on GitHub</p>
        <p>Add Dutch translation. Contributions to add additional languages are welcome</p>
        <p>Always use maximum resolution in full screen mode</p>
        <p>Make window resizable and scale dynamically in windowed mode</p>
        <p>Allow opening the menu with middle click on the mouse</p>
        <p>Add opening animation to levels</p>
        <p>Improve matching animation</p>
        <p>Add credits screen</p>
        <p>Move game modes into own screen</p>
        <p>Fix Playstation Portable version</p>
        <p>Improve performance in Playstation Portable version</p>
        <p>Improve text positioning on all menus</p>
        <p>Decrease the size of binary on all platforms</p>
        <p>Log exceptions thanks to mardy on GitHub</p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="1.1" date="2022-11-10">
      <description>
        <p>Add a short explanation for each mode to the main menu</p>
        <p>Overlapping score indicators are now added together</p>
        <p>Linux AppImage should now work on more systems</p>
        <p>Preparations for a Flathub release</p>
      </description>
    </release>

    <release version="1.0" date="2022-03-09">
      <description>
        <p>First Release</p>
      </description>
    </release>
  </releases>

  <content_rating type="oars-1.1"/>
</component>
